# **Dmitrijs**

# Starcenko

Software Developer [Mobile | Frontend | Backend]



dlstarcenko@gmail.com



Ireland - Dublin



distarcenko



dls-web.github.io

#### **PROFILE**

Highly focused software developer with five years experience in a variety of development positions. Organised, methodical and a keen eye for detail results in solid coding and trustworthy software programmes.

Understanding client requirements and communicating the progress of projects are core values in achieving long lasting relationships

#### **LINGUSTIC SKILLS**

English - Fluent Russian - Native Latvian - Basic

#### CODING / SCRIPTING

JavaScript | TypeScript Python | Java | C#

#### **FRONTEND**

Angular [2 - 8] | MVC HTML | CSS | SCSS

#### **MOBILE (Cross Platform)**

**Appcelerator | PWA** 

#### **BACKEND**

.NET | Node | Spring

#### **DATABASES**

SQL | NoSQL

CI

Jenkins

#### **VERSION CONTROL**

Git | TFS | SVN

#### **TESTING**

**Jasmin** 

#### **PACKAGE MANAGER**

NPM | Nuget



## **EXPERIENCE**

# **Software Developer**

Jan 2014 - Present

### Insights

- Mobile App Development
- Web Development
- Backend Bug Fixes
- SQL Scripting
- WiKi Updates
- Report Generation
- Support

#### **Mobile Game Developer**

Sep 2013 – Nov 2013 Short Term Contract

#### Ninja Kiwi Europe

- Develop game mechanics
- C++ Coding

# Mobile Game Developer 3D Artist and Animator

Jun 2013 - Aug 2013

# Dare to Be Digital 2013

- Develop 2 player Co-Op Game
- Create 3D Characters/Models
- Animate Models
- Present Game to Public

#### **Software Developer**

Jun 2012 - Jul 2012

# C.A.S.A.L.A: Summer Internship

- Java Software Development
- Developed 2D/3D Player



#### **TRAINING**

# **Security Training**

**Jul 2019** 

#### I-I 0040

**ASP.NET Training** 

Apr 2019

#### NCC

**Penetration Testing** 

#### QA

**Building Effective Websites Using Microsoft MVC** 



# **EDUCATION**

#### 2017-2019

Ireland, Dublin

## **National College of Ireland**

MSc in Cyber Security (Thesis in Progress)

### 2009 - 2013

Ireland, Dundalk

#### **Dundalk Institute of Technology**

**BSc in Computing in Games Development (1:1)** 

# 2009

Ireland, Ashbourne

# **Leaving Certificate**